Poor soul.
What is he still doing up there?
Waiting on the coroner.
Careful. Slow drip.
A single shot through the back.
Looks like he got off a few
rounds before he hit him.
- 9-millimeter, maybe?
- It looks like. Was anybody here?
Janitor came in at 7:00.
Says the victim's name is Jeremy Reese.
- Lived here in Clearlake.
- Did the janitor see anyone?
It was empty. It's a private gym.
Victim had a key,
but it's not in his bag.
His car's still in the lot.
Robbery, maybe?
We should go to his apartment now.
- Have you seen Jane?
- Nope.
- Good morning, Lisbon.
- Don't be so sure. We caught a case.
- I've been alerted.
- "And yet you're not here in Clearlake."
- Well, I'm busy.
- Jane. You can't obsess like this.
Obsess?
I know that I've met Red John now.
Shook his hand.
I have what you coppers call a lead.
- Yes, but we have a fresh body here.
- I think you're obsessing.
I will text you the address.
I'll see you there.
Jeremy Reese. No record.
Not even a parking ticket.
What do you think?
I think he graduated from college
about three years ago. He's single.
He works in the sciences.
Uh, maybe a biologist.
He's from back east.
Likes puzzles.
- No family in the area.
- Yeah. He was a botanist.
He worked at a local pot farm
Westerly Organics.
Pot farm? Oh, that follows.
His last phone call was
to Alice Burns last night.
She's an old college Professor of his.
Yes, that would be her
in the photograph.
I'm guessing the parents couldn't
make it out for the graduation.
- Also this, um, apartment's been tossed.
- By who? Martha Stewart?
No, by someone who was searching
for something of incredible value.
They wanted to try and put the place
back together but they failed.
Incredible value? There's about 200 bucks
worth of furniture in here.
Allow me to show you.
This plaid shirt here is
in amongst the stripes. Hard to miss.
- That is a wall.
- So it is.
Bear with me.
Eh...
Yes. Uh, it's back over here.
There it is.
See these two textbooks?
They're out of order.
Volume one is next to volume three.
- A safe.
- Found his keys.
- It's empty.
- Killer got what they came for.
We need to find someone
who knows what was in that safe.
I think this puzzle box is the key.
Whatever's in here
was important enough to hide
but not valuable enough
to put in that safe.
What do you think it is?
Well, we don't know yet.
It's a puzzle.
- Cho, crack it open.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
It's my puzzle.
All mine.
Hey, boss.
We didn't get much
off Jeremy's phone.
Mostly calls
to his family in Boston.
Call his parents
and give them the bad news.
Tell Rigsby to check
his e-mails and his texts.
We need to find out
what was in that safe.
I'm on it.
Hello. I'm looking
for Agent Teresa Lisbon.
Mrs. Burns. You were the last person
Jeremy called before he was murdered.
- Do you need a moment?
- Uh, no, I'll be fine. I'm okay.
- Why did Jeremy call you?
- Just to talk. I was his advisor in college.
Was he having problems?
He was upset over a disagreement
with his boss.
Not surprising if you know Matthew Gold.
A bit of a medical marijuana celebrity.
- He owns Westerly Organic?
- Yeah.
Jeremy did not smoke, by the way.
Genetic research around marijuana
is simply
the most exciting place
to be for a young botanist.
It was a good use of his skills.
- Did he go into specifics about the fight?
- No. He just said that he was anxious
over friction with his boss.
Jeremy could be...
Secretive.
We're plant people.
Did he have any enemies?
Anyone with an ax to grind?
No. He was kind
and generous to a fault.
Do you always keep in touch
with your students after graduation?
No. Jeremy's mother died
a few years ago
and with my son in Houston
we were a...
Pretend family.
What are you sick with?
It started in my stomach
and spread to the lymph nodes.
School wants me to wrap it up.
I told them, "eh, one more semester."
He, um...
I'm sorry.
Um, brought me my prescription
every two weeks
and we would do the crossword.
He liked puzzles.
Any kind. Didn't matter.
- Your doctor lets you smoke?
- He prescribed it.
I'm dying.
It helps with the pain.
And helps me eat
my husband's cooking.
Uh, just... just
one more question...
you don't happen to know
how to open this, do you?
No. Jeremy made me one
and I forgot how it went.
Ah. Clever kid, huh?
Hi, there.
We're with the CBI.
We're looking for your boss,
Matthew gold.
That's me.
Can we talk in the barn?
I'm just hanging some buds.
- Hangin' some buds.
- Well, someone's gotta do it.
You know, I... I never had a kid
that smart on the farm.
In five years, he'd... he'd have
been running this place.
- Were any of your other workers jealous?
- No, everyone loved Jeremy.
They'll all help plan a memorial.
We're like minds here, you know?
Dedicated to organic growing.
- None of that indoor chemical garbage.
- So, uh, how do I get involved?
Do I have to get a prescription
or join a club or something?
You'll be in the cooperative if you have
a condition we can help with.
We, uh, we supply patients
all over the state.
California says I can grow
no more than exactly 99 plants.
Uncle Sam says
I'm a narco-terrorist.
- I choose to side with California.
- Tough business.
Eh, I just wish I could grow more.
But these laws...
I'm no businessman.
Used to be.
I gave up a software career to come
out here and make a difference.
- We're healers, you know?
- Healers with an armed guard?
Oh, Vick, yeah. He, uh, keeps
our intellectual property safe.
We grow the dankest weed
in the valley thanks to these.
"Dank"? I'm, uh,
I'm guessing that means "good"?
Well, our patients like it.
Jeremy helped me grow that crop.
We won highest T.H.C.
at Mendocino Weed Wars.
It's a cross between reclining Buddha
and some wicked Afghani stuff.
I've, uh, turned down
offers from the cartels
who don't exactly abide
by the social contract, hence Vick.
When was the last time
you saw Jeremy?
He was out of here
at 5:00 yesterday.
Uh, the kids cook dinner together
but, I don't know, Jeremy
usually did his own thing.
Uh, we heard that Jeremy
was fighting with his boss.
Fighting? No, no.
We...we were eye to eye.
We were just planting next year's crop.
- I can show you.
- Okay.
Danky.
Hi. I was hoping
you could help me.
- Keep hoping.
- You're not scared of cops but, uh...
you tried to avoid
eye contact back there.
Because you're loyal to Jeremy?
You think he was into something
that he shouldn't have been?
- You're reaching.
- Always.
Dippin' into
the company stash, huh?
And don't deny it.
You're as high as a kite right now
and I can guarantee you
that's against company policy.
Big whoop.
So you know I'm baked.
Oh, you're not just baked.
You are baked.
- What's your name?
- Carson.
What are you protecting
Jeremy from, Carson? He's dead.
Okay.
Like, six months back...
My car was jacked up in an accident.
Jeremy gave me money to fix it.
8 g's. Like it was nothing.
That's a lot of money.
You think he was dealing
the marijuana on the side?
Hey, I asked him.
He said, "hell no"
I didn't care.
But if Matthew found out,
he'd kill him.
That's good to know.
Thank you, Carson.
You need some more eye drops.
Just maybe a breath mint.
Secret's safe with me.
No big-ticket items
on Jeremy's credit card.
I don't know
what Jane's talking about.
Kid lived cheap.
Yeah, but if you look
at his bank accounts, plain vanilla.
Then eight months ago,
he opens a savings account
and he gets once-monthly direct deposits
from some company in the Caymans.
- 10 grand a pop.
- Shady.
'Sup, ladies?
- Hey.
- Agent Wade.
Gang unit has a tip
on a counterfeiting ring
running out of a garage
on west capitol.
Rapid response team
is up for the bust.
- Nice. Now?
- Roll call in 30.
- I squared it with your cute boss.
- I'm in.
- Uh, we have work to do.
- I'll have him back in a few hours, dad.
Look, if you're the rapid response team
shouldn't you be sliding down fire poles
not hanging around here
for 30 minutes?
So Jeremy was making money
on the side.
More than he was making
at Westerly Organics.
Maybe that's the boss
he was fighting with.
Except I can't figure out
who was paying him.
A company in Romania that was
incorporated in the Caymans.
Keep digging.
We need to figure out
what was in that safe.
Uh, what do you think
it was, drugs?
He had too much respect for his work
to sell it in Ziploc baggies.
Well, it wasn't cash.
All the money deposited in his account's
still there except for 8 grand.
Which he gave to his friend.
Preliminary forensics report puts
the time of death around 6:00 a.m.
No one had seen Jeremy for 12 hours.
Maybe he was moonlighting.
- Might explain those deposits.
- Jane? Thoughts?
- I'm puzzled.
- That's evidence.
I want you to get it
to technical services
and have it opened, on my desk
in the morning. Are we good?
You seem a little obsessed
with evaluating our status.
Is it good, bad...
I mean, we're alive.
The guy that made this is dead.
By comparison, I think
we're doing very well.
Tomorrow morning.
Police! Hands in the air!
Hands in the air!
Put them now!
- Up against the wall!
- I got him.
Hands in the air!
- Kimball?
- Summer?
- Hands in the air!
- Already done.
Down on the ground!
Well... do...uh...
Uh, hands in the air or...or down
on the ground? I'm a little confused.
- A tobacco laboratory?
- Well, I didn't know what it was.
- Oh, so you just broke in?
- I left you a voicemail.
How did you get the box open?
Francesca Ehrlich
with JG Allen Tobacco.
- This is Stuart Davis, my boss.
- Ah. Patrick Jane, consultant.
This, uh, isn't my boss.
- I am Teresa Lisbon, and I am his boss.
- So you're responsible for Mr. Jane
compromising a top-secret
research facility?
Jeremy had a key. What was he doing
with a key to a tobacco laboratory?
Well, Jeremy is...
was... a freelance botanist.
He worked nights and weekends for us
about nine months?
- Yeah.
- And what's your role here?
I'm senior vice president
in charge of new products.
New products?
Like, uh, the, uh...
Mar...marijuana?
Our analysis is that marijuana
will be decriminalized in our lifetime.
And JG Allen will be
ready to embrace that market.
Still a controversial area,
hence the secrecy.
So you were having Jeremy Reese
grow you some corporate weed?
He was developing a fungus-resistant
mass-producible marijuana strain.
Project Turbo Wolf.
It was part of my portfolio.
Project Turbo Wolf?
Uh, we heard that Jeremy
was arguing with his boss.
But it wasn't at his day job, was it?
It was you.
Well, disagreements between researchers
and the product team are common.
And there was a spirited
discussion a few days ago.
We haven't seen Jeremy since.
And... how do I put this delicately?
He had just harvested
his Turbo Wolf seeds.
- And we can't seem to find them.
- That may be what was in the safe.
What safe?
Well, it seems someone
may have bogarted your stash.
Well, we have to find those seeds.
I mean, this project will be worth billions
to the company one day.
- Billions? Wow.
- How much is it worth today?
Well, I'm sure our competitors
would pay millions to acquire it.
I'll bet you dollars to doughnuts
I can find your seeds.
Let's start with a tour
of the lab, shall we?
Looks like your marijuana
project is well funded.
Well, it's not all
just marijuana, per se.
We're also developing a range
of non-narcotic products.
- Jeremy's desk, I imagine?
- Yes, sir.
It's exactly as he left it.
What's the story
with this box?
Because whenever I touch it,
you blink rapidly.
- Uh, nothing.
- Could you step back, Mr. Pierce?
Thank you. Making me nervous.
- That looks like a bug.
- Cool.
- Summer Edgecombe. Wow.
- Yeah.
That's not...
that's not yours, is it?
No. She's in town for her wedding
to the baby's father.
- Gonna be a pretty big deal, apparently.
- Wow.
You said that.
Yep. You dodged a bullet
when you let that one slip away.
Oh, my God. Kimball.
Can you believe this?
I'm in town for, like, five days and boom...
here we are. Like old times.
Yeah. Just like.
Summer, why didn't you call me
if you were in trouble?
- I wasn't in trouble.
- Well, you are now.
Oh, please. This?
You can make this go away.
I'm a confidential informant.
I got juice in this building.
Yeah, but you were in a garage
full of phony cash.
No. No, no, no. No.
Chuck said we were
just going for a ride.
I was bored, so I went.
And then he said he had
to stop by some friends'.
And... well, when I got there,
I realized it was a bad deal.
By then, it was too late.
Eight months pregnant?
How stupid do you think
I think you are?
Uh, I swear, I have nothing to do
with this counterfeiting, or whatever.
- Like, at all. Ask those guys.
- Well, they're not talking.
Well, what are we gonna do?
The wedding's in two days.
- I... I can't stay here.
- Your buddy Chuck could help.
- You don't believe me.
- Doesn't matter what I believe.
It matters to me, Kimball.
I... I did what you said.
I went to Seattle. I got cleaned up.
And... and Marshall, he's nice.
He's... he's in real estate.
We have a house.
That's good. And if this guy's
halfway decent, he'll understand.
No, no, no. He can't know.
He thinks I'm at my sister's.
Look, I love him.
But there's things about me...
Please?
No one else is gonna help me.
Tell me where to find Chuck.
- You need to let her go.
- I knew this was coming.
Look, I know the woman.
She was my C.I.
I heard she was
a lot more than that.
Look, she didn't do this.
She was just in the wrong place.
Maybe she was in the right place
as a lookout.
No. I know her.
And I believe her.
This is my case.
I'm charging her.
Now what?
Cop to cop, you know
how this goes.
Just give me what I need,
and let's get out of here.
Davis won't say this,
but three days ago
I was called upstairs
to restrain the kid.
He's screaming, "it's my work."
The project's completed, right?
They wanna move the seeds
into secure storage.
That's when the kid lost it.
I'm gonna need access
to all the recordings you made.
Then you're gonna need
a court order. Cop to cop.
- Cho's awfully trusting.
- It's from the rapid response raid.
It's counterfeit.
There's bags and bags of it.
Bags and bags of it?
Imagine that.
You like the security
guard for the murder?
Pierce? Eh.
He's well trained, but a lapdog.
Lifestyle's too comfy
to risk murder.
That may be true,
but I'm gonna hold him
until I can get a warrant
to search the tobacco lab.
- Did you check the security logs yet?
- Yeah. On the night of his murder
Jeremy swiped into
JG Allen Tobacco at 8:00 p.m.
That makes sense.
They were planning to take
his work to cold storage
so he went to the lab
to take back his seeds.
Seeds worth millions of dollars.
Certainly worth killing for.
Find the seeds,
you'll find the killer.
Grace, do you have
any of Jeremy's notebooks from the lab?
Uh, yeah. Sure.
Right here.
A lot of it's gibberish.
Like a code?
There's a long tradition of scientists
that disguise their thoughts in code.
- Let me see.
- You have an idea?
Eh, more of a notion.
We need to interview every
employee from the tobacco lab.
Rigsby, run background checks.
And let's get the execs back here.
CBI, ma'am.
We have information
Chuck Calloway's been staying here.
I don't know any Chuck.
Really? You're his sister,
so how's that work
- You got it?
- I got it!
- Police brutality, man!
- Not yet!
- Give me your arms.
- I'm not resisting!
- Pierce, isn't it?
- What do you want?
What do I want? I want your professional
opinion if that's okay.
Uh, I found this note
in Jeremy's apartment.
That's actually a copy.
You know that name? Olivier Gans?
No. Should I?
Ah, he's a pharmaceutical
company buyer, middle man.
- You think Jeremy knew him?
- Well, we don't know.
As you can see, the rest
of the note is in code
- and I can't... I can't crack it, so...
- Well, maybe I could.
Sure. Be my guest.
If anything pops out,
just let me know.
Who's Olivier Gans?
Uh, I don't know.
Made him up.
- How do you know Summer?
- Oh, we're friends.
She and my cousin hooked up once.
Maybe more than once.
- A few times, actually.
- I got it.
Now what were you two doing
at that warehouse?
It's okay.
No one knows you're here.
Shall we go another round?
I did some work for these guys.
I'd buy some stuff with their bills
and then return it for cash.
I don't care about
your criminal offenses.
I want to know what Summer Edgecombe
was doing there.
Oh, dude... These are not good people.
Okay? They...they scare me.
I was dropping off some cash,
but I was a little light
and I thought they'd be chill
if I brought a pregnant lady.
You're an idiot, Chuck.
And I need names.
Everything you know
about that counterfeit ring.
- And if I can't remember?
- Do you need another enemy?
Researchers consistently fail to understand
the importance of their own work.
Is that why you spy on people?
We have every right to maintain
operational oversight of our employees...
- freelancers included.
- Maybe legally speaking.
- How do you feel about it, Francesca?
- Well...
I chose not to inform Francesca
of my instructions to Pierce.
So you don't trust
your executives, either?
I wonder if there's hidden
microphones in your office.
There's not.
There's not, Francesca.
- Of course.
- We'll find out soon enough.
We're working on getting a warrant
to obtain your security recordings.
Uh, excuse me. Olivier Gans...
are you familiar with him?
Big-time underworld pharmaceutical buyer.
Very clandestine.
That looks like Jeremy's writing.
Yeah, we found it
among his papers.
We have reason to believe that he
and this Gans guy were in contact.
And you ask if I trust my people?
Do you think Jeremy was
shopping around Turbo Wolf?
Well, maybe. This guy's very connected.
He deals all over the globe.
- And this code?
- Well, yeah. We're stumped.
Maybe somebody on your team
can get to the bottom of it.
- When is Jeremy's memorial?
- Tomorrow morning.
Sorry for the intrusion.
D.D.A. Ardiles.
Charles Calloway.
- Agent Cho, always a pleasure.
- You can call me Chuck.
Ah, I think I will. Chuck.
So... we looked into some
of the names you gave Agent Cho.
If these claims hold water
this counterfeiting ring
you're hooked into is quite extensive.
Well, dude
these guys run California, okay?
- And you're prepared to inform on them?
- Yeah.
Well, I mean,
for the right price.
- Let me guess. Full immunity.
- I can't do time, man.
- Hey.
- Oh, yeah. Uh...
Uh, Summer Edgecombe...
- I only come on board if she walks.
- Now the picture comes into focus.
Look, Summer wasn't involved.
She was just there
when the raid went down.
Wasn't Summer Edgecombe
a former C.I. herself?
She proved to be an asset
to the CBI on many occasions. Yeah.
Nothing else?
You and Summer?
Look, are you gonna make
a deal or not?
It's always something
with you guys.
You know what? I wasn't looking forward
to prosecuting a pregnant woman anyhow.
Welcome aboard, Chuck.
We'll draw up the paperwork.
Say what you will about hippies.
They throw a good funeral.
Sure, if classical guitar
is your bag.
So did you get that puzzle box open?
- Yes. Magnets.
- Magnets.
He would have loved
that you figured that out.
He didn't have a lot of people
that could play at his level.
Yeah, well, that's a curse
some of us live with.
Uh, excuse me, please.
Hey, nice of you to come.
Well, I had some business
in the area.
Thought I'd stop by, show my respects.
Some business?
You have a lead?
Uh, it's okay.
You can trust Carson.
Well, we have a...
confidential but, uh, very solid lead.
- Olivier Gans? Who's that?
- He's a big-time pharmaceutical buyer.
Uh, shady character, deep pockets
smoke-filled rooms.
Was Jeremy trying to sell our strains?
- Did you know about this?
- What? No. No, I swear.
We'll find out soon enough
when we can crack Jeremy's code.
Uh, please excuse me.
Hi, Lisbon.
I don't know what game you're playing
but I think you're getting carried away
- with this Olivier Gans thing.
- How so?
I... I just got a call from the vice
President of something or other
of JG Allen Enterprises.
- They're up in arms about Gans.
- "Really?"
They think he's trying
to steal Turbo Wolf.
Well, he hasn't yet,
but he might soon.
- We should meet at his hotel.
- The imaginary man has a hotel?
- That's right.
- Is this hotel imaginary, too?
Oh, no, very real.
It's, uh, the Vista in Clearlake.
I'll meet you there in an hour. Bye.
"Jeremy was killed for his seeds."
But the killer's faced
with a problem.
Who wants to pay millions of dollars
for a handful of seeds?
- Somebody who knows their value.
- Yeah, well, that's a very limited market
and with a murder investigation afoot
I am betting that the killer
is desperate enough
to sell now
and get out of town.
- So you made up a fake buyer?
- Olivier Gans.
And the rest of the note
is Caesar code.
Exactly the kind of thing that Jeremy
would use to hide his information.
It translates to "3:00 p.m.
Friday at the Vista."
Who's gonna figure that out?
Whoever has millions
of dollars at stake.
Assuming they do,
we can't arrest somebody
- for knocking on a door.
- I'm well aware of that.
That's why we're gonna get them
to sell us the merchandise.
Olivier? You ready?
Uh, yeah, lose the tie.
- I don't think Olivier Gans is a tie guy.
- Okay, you got it.
See that face? That's exactly why
I didn't tell you the plan.
- It's not a good plan.
- It's a good enough plan
and Rigsby's wearing
one of those ear thingies.
I will talk him through the con.
He'll be fine.
What if the killer
doesn't show up?
Then we go back
to old-fashioned police work.
But this way, we get to enjoy
some room service.
Please, have a seat.
- Enough of the cheese.
- "I'm hungry."
- Jane, it's 3:15.
- Patience.
Hello?
Yeah. Send him up.
"On the way."
- Mr. Gans, is it?
- And who are you?
Jeremy couldn't be here.
You'll conduct business with me today.
- I'm Francesca.
- Yeah. Come in.
Once she makes her offer,
you sweep in and make your arrest.
If she makes the offer.
- How do I know you're not a cop?
- "Easy there, tiger."
"Chicken's already in the coop.
Let's not overdo it."
The cops don't have the real deal.
I do.
There's only one
Turbo Wolf.
- Would you like to sample the product?
- Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Get her to show you
the seeds.
That's nice.
Really smooth.
It's a 60/40
Indica dominant hybrid
ideal for commercial production
of smokable applications
as well as for pills, oral sprays,
and dermal patches.
Strong.
And, uh, where are the seeds?
Right here.
I'm going in.
- Who's that?
- Uh, it's not us.
- "Just... just answer it."
- Y-you just stay there. I got this.
- Hi. Uh, you're Gans?
- Depends.
You're looking for Turbo Wolf, right?
Uh, could you pass the cheese plate?
This is getting good.
Get in.
They can't both have
Turbo Wolf.
No, but one of them
killed Jeremy for it.
All right,
then I'm pulling the plug.
We can bring them in
and talk to them.
Pish posh. He's doing a great job.
Let's just see what happens.
- What's she doing here?
- Me? What are you doing here?
You guys know each other?
That's nice.
- The pot business is fairly small.
- Though I'm in the pot business, and...
I don't know either of you.
Am I talking loud?
You're doing fine, Rigsby.
What we need to figure out...
the story with Matthew Gold.
Please...
Oh, I know what to do.
- You do?
- Maybe. We divide and conquer
Give them a chance
to split the money.
Rigsby, we're gonna play
a little game.
It's called "repeat after me."
"I can understand you're nervous..."
I understand you're nervous.
"You're both trying
to sell a dead man's work."
You're both trying to sell
a dead man's product.
Here's the thing.
My client just wants results.
"They're not interested
in provenance."
They're not concerned
with provolone... provenance.
They... they're not
concerned with provenance.
They don't care
where it came from.
"You both claim to have
Turbo Wolf to sell me."
You both claim that you're
selling Turbo Wolf.
Only one of you is right.
"Now I don't have all day
to hash this out..."
So here's what I'm gonna do.
I have 4 million dollars.
"That's the price that
Jeremy and I discussed."
"Now..."
I'm willing to buy both your seeds...
"And you guys can split the money.
Or..."
Or...
One of you can prove
that you have the real deal.
And you get it all.
$2 million each?
I can live on that.
I'm sure you can but I didn't
come here for half of anything.
What are you talking about?
Let's take the deal.
Why?
I don't know what you have
but my product is authentic.
I hired the team that grew it.
- You poached a kid that I trained.
- Thanks for the head start.
We're getting into the weeds here.
I'm on it.
- "Okay, let's not get personal."
- Let's not get, uh, personal.
Let's... have some cheese, huh?
If we can't make a deal
I'm gonna walk out of here right now.
Fine. I'm not splitting.
You're in over your head, Matthew.
All right, yeah. Yeah.
She might have grown this stuff
but Jeremy came to me when she tried
to put his product on ice.
I convinced...
I convinced him to steal
his seeds from the lab.
The same seeds I took from his safe.
She's got nothing.
- Oh, my God. You killed him?
- Yeah, what?
You need me to spell it out
for you?
I'm not walking away
with half now. I want it all!
- Okay, hands in the air!
- What the hell are you talking about?
- Um, I... I mean, nobody move!
- Whoa.
I'm a cop.
Just... nobody move. See?
Matthew Gold,
you're under arrest for murder!
- Rigsby, hook her up, too.
- Wait... for what?
- Industrial espionage, to start with.
- Yeah, I got it.
Nope. I'm...
I'm gonna sit down.
Let me see your hands.
Now! You, too.
- Boss, is it okay if I sit down?
- You are sitting down, Rigsby.
I felt betrayed, you know?
That he'd go behind
my back like that.
And for a tobacco company?
Then I figured
they gave him resources I couldn't.
"And when they told him they were putting
his project on hold for who knows how long"
- "you convinced him to steal it back."
- "I told him with..."
my reputation, we could
offer his strain to the world.
But that was never your intent.
I should be rich by now, you know?
But this whole industry, the...
the rules change every day.
I knew when he came to me, I...
I could take this stuff, you know?
I knew he'd be at the gym.
"I tried to tell myself
the gun was just there"
"so he'd give me
the keys to the safe."
"But... I knew."
I had already gone too far.
I gotta hand it to her.
She played you all.
- What are you talking about?
- Francesca.
She just confessed.
Once Jeremy's work
went into cold storage
she knew he'd sneak back
into the lab to steal his seeds.
"That's why she switched
them out first"
"so she could sell them
for herself on the black market."
You mean Francesca had
the Turbo Wolf all along?
Yep.
You killed your protege for a handful
of worthless hemp seeds.
Agent Wade.
- I hope this Summer girl's worth it.
- It's not like that.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Look, I should have come to you
before going to the D.D.A.'s office.
- I would have shut you down.
- I wouldn't have blamed you.
- So you're not mad?
- Mad? This is about trust.
I put together a rapid response team.
I gotta know we're watching
each other's back.
- You went behind mine.
- It'll never happen again.
That's for sure.
Kimball.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What'd you think, I was
just gonna disappear?
- I wouldn't put it past you.
- Well, you saved the wedding.
And this was on the way, so...
- Uh, babe?
- Oh, Marshall, come here.
I want you to meet my friend,
Agent Cho.
Agent Cho, this is Marshall.
- Uh, the fiancé.
- It's nice to meet you.
You got any firemen to say
good-bye to, or what?
Uh, no offense, buddy,
but, uh, we got a thing.
Just give me a minute,
would you?
He's a good guy.
He really is.
We're heading down to Pismo
for the honeymoon.
- It's nice down there.
- Yeah.
Thank you, Kimball.
I promise I won't bug you anymore.
I'm gonna be good.
Good-bye, Summer.
Good luck.
I'd kiss you, but Marshall
gets crazy jealous.
This is so annoying.
I can't find my keys.
- Did you check your desk?
- Of course I...
Oh. Here they are.
Silly me.
You keep a hammer
in your desk.
You only think you know
everything about me.